Hello Hello friends welcome to one
and in today's video we will see
ICICI's final against criminal listen
in Google account
that legislative institution behind one thing right now whose name
is junior doo doo doo
nothing it is not that no come and
give
and then you can see the link of planning and children
cigarette Switzerland page when you
people which is
this combination hair tips saving tom
and jerry goodbye let's use
[music]
now you can open and operate
child account right in all the viewers stage
color according to state cut minute
unit limit triangle you will get ₹100 we
primitive with it and for shopping and this
is directly this point us zor meaning of
standard will be free free free
if you match us well you
can read it below you have
star star you must be thinking that
people above ten years of age have a separate
account in this you will also have parents half
guardian start pred Bihar means Shyam  So I will get a
car, mobile smart 40 days
give me, means you can do whatever you want
and you need proof, you need a photo of the car - in the
form of and in this a group d a
proof of minor should get a photography
and declaration reminder should be done
with declaration whose ID and
proof should be taken by a car and search and this
year's entire channel,
here you have the smell of all sea and
young star you can see below from default and from junior
to senior you will have to do the plane landed central you will have to do
monthly current situation different ginger, you
cannot go and you have looted the charge
and subscribe subscribe and if the charge is
not complete then you
can complete it by going to the link description, so today's video is
yes sorry friends, now very sorry ice cream could
not produce much time, the
last of the mighty war memorials from here
you will also have to go
online, you can like both of them and
ask by commenting, you can do it, you can comment
hindi.com in Hindi,
this is the name of every salt to apply to me, this is
tea from this  I can reply this much in the comments
and do subscribe.